Guide to Chancellor of the University of Pittsburgh, Edward H. Litchfield, Administrative Files, 1956-1965 UA.2.10.1956-1965
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Subject List, 1956-1965; I.
  - Public and International Affairs, Graduate School of, January 1965-July 1965 (Box 109, Folder 890)
  - Public and International Affairs, Graduate School of, December 1960-December 1964 (Box 110, Folder 891-896)
  - Public and International Affairs, Graduate School of, June 1958-November 1960 (Box 111, Folder 897-902)
  - Public and International Affairs, Graduate School of, August 1956-May 1958 (Box 112, Folder 903-908)
  - Public Relations, Director of, January 1961-February 1966 (Box 112, Folder 909-911)
  - Public Relations, Director of, August 1959-December 1960 (Box 112, Folder 912)
    Scope and Content Notes
    There are also some scattered memoranda from 1955-1958 dealing with the Schenley Hotel.
  - Public Relations, Director of, Survey of Attitudes Toward Pittsburgh Universities, 1961 (Box 112, Folder 913)
  - Public Relations, Counselor of, January 1956-July 1959 (Box 112, Folder 914-916)
  - Public Relations, Counselor of, January 1955-December 1955 (Box 114, Folder 917)
  - Purchasing, Director of (Box 114, Folder 918)
  - P General
    - Pace - Parry (Box 114, Folder 919)
    - Pasek - Penn (Box 114, Folder 920)
    - Pennsylvania Association - Pennsylvania Political Science (Box 114, Folder 921)
    - Pennsylvania Rail Road - Pettrigrow (Box 114, Folder 922)
    - Pfister - Pittsburgh Athletic (Box 114, Folder 923)
    - Pittsburgh Baseball - Pittsburgh Progress (Box 114, Folder 924)
    - Pittsburgh Public - Pittsburgh Weekly (Box 115, Folder 925)
    - Placement - Porter (Box 115, Folder 926)
    - Portland - Prince (Box 115, Folder 927)
    - Princeton - Pymatuning (Box 115, Folder 928)
  - Q General (Box 115, Folder 929)
  - Radiation Laboratory (Box 115, Folder 930)
  - Radiation Safety Committee (Box 115, Folder 931)
  - Railway Research Institute (Box 115, Folder 932)
  - Rankin, Alan C., 1955-1959 (Box 116, Folder 933-935)
    Related Material
    After 1959, see General Affairs, Assistant Chancellor for.
  - Regional Commission on Education Coordination (Box 116, Folder 936)
  - Regional Industrial Development Corporation (Box 116, Folder 937)
  - Regional Programs, Vice Chancellor, October 1961-April 1965 (Box 116, Folder 938-939)
  - Regional Programs, Vice Chancellor, Washington Office (Box 116, Folder 940)
  - Regional Programs, Vice Chancellor, Ellwood City (Box 117, Folder 941)
  - Regional Programs, Vice Chancellor, Franklin (Box 117, Folder 942)
  - Registrar, 1957-1961 (Box 117, Folder 943)
  - Registrar, 1955-1956 (Box 117, Folder 944)
  - Religion, Board of (Box 117, Folder 945)
  - Religious Survey Committee, June 1954-May 1956 (Box 117, Folder 946-947)
  - Research Park (Box 117, Folder 948)
  - Residential Seminars of World Affairs (Box 117, Folder 949)
  - Retailing, School of (Box 117, Folder 950)
  - Retirement Pension Material, 1955-1958 (Box 118, Folder 951-953)
  - Re-Training Centers (Box 118, Folder 954)
  - Russian Rectors (Box 118, Folder 955)
  - R General
    - Racine - Raymond (Box 118, Folder 956)
    - Rea - Reynolds (Box 118, Folder 957)
    - Rhee - Roberts (Box 118, Folder 958)
    - Robertson - Roper (Box 118, Folder 959)
    - Rosa - Rothert (Box 119, Folder 960)
    - Rothman - Rynerson (Box 119, Folder 961)
  - Sabbaticals (Box 119, Folder 962)
  - Salary Statistics (Comparison with other Universities) (Box 119, Folder 963)
  - Salk, Dr. Jonas (Box 119, Folder 964)
  - Salk, Dr. Jonas, Comments on Salk Affair (Box 119, Folder 965)
  - Salk Hall Renovation (Box 119, Folder 966)
  - Sarah Mellon Scaife Foundation, December 1964, March 1965-July 1965 (Box 119, Folder 967-968)
  - Sarah Mellon Scaife Foundation, December 1955-October 1964 (Box 120, Folder 969-972)
  - Scaife Hall Dedication (Box 120, Folder 973)
  - Scheduling Policy, Committee on (Box 120, Folder 974)
  - Scholarships and Student Aid, Committee on (Box 120, Folder 975)
  - Secretary of the University, June 1963-July 1965 (Box 120, Folder 976-977)
  - Secretary of the University, September 1958 May 1963 (Box 121, Folder 978-984)
  - Secretary of the University, November 1955-August 1958 (Box 122, Folder 985-990)
  - Seminars (Box 122, Folder 991)
  - Seminar in Administrative Theory (Box 122, Folder 992)
  - University Senate, Committee to Appraise the Reorganized Senate (Box 122, Folder 993)
  - University Senate, Budget Policies Committee (Box 122, Folder 994)
  - University Senate, Committee on Committees (Box 122, Folder 995)
  - University Senate, Educational Policies (Box 122, Folder 996)
  - University Senate, Executive Committee (Box 122, Folder 997)
  - University Senate, Faculty Health and Welfare Committee (Box 123, Folder 998)
  - University Senate, Faculty Participation in Policy Making (Box 123, Folder 999)
  - University Senate, Faculty Personnel Advisory Committee (Box 123, Folder 1000)
  - University Senate, Student Relations (Box 123, Folder 1001)
  - University Senate, Tenure and Academic Freedom (Box 123, Folder 1002)
  - University Senate Council, January 1961-June 1965 (Box 123, Folder 1003-1008)
  - University Senate Council, September 1955-December 1960 (Box 124, Folder 1009-1015)
  - Senatorial Scholarships (Box 124, Folder 1016)
  - Shakespeare Festival (Box 125, Folder 1017)
  - Slides (Box 125, Folder 1018)
  - Smoking Policy, University Committee on (Box 125, Folder 1019)
  - Social Sciences, Division of, 1958 - 1965 (Box 125, Folder 1020-1021)
  - Social Professions Quadrangle (Box 125, Folder 1022)
  - Social Work, Graduate School of, 1955-1965 (Box 125, Folder 1023-1025)
  - Social Work, Graduate School of, Board of Visitors (Box 126, Folder 1026)
  - Social Work, Graduate School of, Search Committee for Dean of the Graduate School of Social Work (Box 126, Folder 1027)
  - Sociology, Department of (Box 126, Folder 1028)
  - Space Research Coordination Center, 1962-1965 (Box 126, Folder 1029-1033)
  - Speakers Bureau (Box 126, Folder 1034)
  - Special Fellowship Committee (Box 126, Folder 1035)
  - Speech, Department of (Box 127, Folder 1036)
  - Spin-off (Box 127, Folder 1037)
  - Sponsored Research Problem (Box 127, Folder 1038)
  - Sports Illustrated (Box 127, Folder 1039)
  - Stadium (as a municipal stadium), 1958-1959 (Box 127, Folder 1040-1041)
  - State Aid, 1963-1965 (Box 127, Folder 1042-1043)
  - State Aid, Addresses, Speeches. Pamphlets (Box 127, Folder 1044)
  - State Aid, Meeting: March 26, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 1045)
  - State Aid, Meeting: January 29, 1964 (Box 128, Folder 1046)
  - State Aid, Meeting: December 9, 1963 (Box 128, Folder 1047)
  - State Aid, House Appropriations Committee Hearing (Box 128, Folder 1048)
  - State Board of Education (Box 128, Folder 1049)
  - State Commission on Athletic Facilities (Box 128, Folder 1050)
  - State Council on Higher Education (Box 128, Folder 1051)
  - State, Department of, 1960-1965 (Box 128, Folder 1052-1054)
  - State Planning Board (Box 128, Folder 1055)
  - Secretary of State (Box 128, Folder 1056)
  - Students, Dean of (Box 128, Folder 1057)
  - Student Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, January 1963-December 1965 (Box 128, Folder 1058-1059)
  - Student Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, June 1958-December 1962 (Box 129, Folder 1060-1068)
  - Student Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, January 1955-May 1958 (Box 130, Folder 1069-1072)
  - Student Affairs, Assistant Chancellor New Applications for Admission, Weekly Progress Reports (Box 130, Folder 1073)
  - Student Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, Recruiting Memoranda (Box 130, Folder 1074)
  - Student Affairs, Assistant Chancellor Alcohol Policy, Intra fraternity Council (Box 130, Folder 1075)
  - Student Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, Student Disciplinary Action (Box 130, Folder 1076)
  - Student Affairs, Assistant Chancellor, Student Affairs Committee (Box 130, Folder 1077)
  - Student Aid, Director of (Box 130, Folder 1078)
  - Student Center in Cathedral of Learning (Box 130, Folder 1079)
  - Student Health Services (Box 130, Folder 1080)
  - Student Luncheons (Box 130, Folder 1081)
  - Student Records, Director of (Box 131, Folder 1082)
  - Student Union (Box 131, Folder 1083)
  - Survey of Administrative Management report, 1954 (Box 131, Folder 1084-1087)
  - Symphony Hall (Box 131, Folder 1088)
  - S General
    - Sabbatical - Sayne (Box 131, Folder 1089)
    - Scaife - Schott (Box 132, Folder 1090)
    - Schramm - Secretary (Box 132, Folder 1091)
    - Security - Shaw (Box 132, Folder 1092)
    - Shea - Sillcox (Box 132, Folder 1093)
    - Silva - Smutnu (Box 132, Folder 1094)
    - Smuts - Social (Box 132, Folder 1095)
    - Speer - Stahl (Box 132, Folder 1096)
    - Stahr - Stern (Box 133, Folder 1097)
    - Stevens - Stuart (Box 133, Folder 1098)
    - Stuck - Studies (Box 133, Folder 1099)
    - Stutz - Syracuse (Box 133, Folder 1100)
  - Teaching, Seminar in College Teaching (Box 133, Folder 1101)
  - Teaching Machines (Box 133, Folder 1102)
  - Tehran University (Box 133, Folder 1103)
  - Temple University (Box 133, Folder 1104)
  - Ten Year Report (Box 134, Folder 1105)
  - TIAA-CREF (Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association - College Retirement Equities Fund) (Box 134, Folder 1106)
  - Triga Reactor (Box 134, Folder 1107)
  - Titusville Campus (Box 134, Folder 1108)
  - Treasurer (Box 134, Folder 1109)
  - Trees Hall Dedication - Fitzgerald Field House (Box 134, Folder 1110)
  - Trimester Plan, January 1959-April 1965 (Box 134, Folder 1111-1114)
  - Trimester Plan, October 1957-December 1958 (Box 135, Folder 1115-1116)
  - Trimester Plan, Conference: March 9, 1961 (Box 135, Folder 1117)
  - Trimester Plan, Conference: June 15, 1960 (Box 135, Folder 1118)
  - Trimester Plan, Correspondence with other Universities (Box 135, Folder 1119)
  - Trimester Plan, Preliminary Planning, August 1958 (Box 135, Folder 1120)
  - Trimester Plan, Preliminary Planning, July 1958 (Box 135, Folder 1121)
  - Trimester Plan, Report of Committee on Trimester Calendar (Box 135, Folder 1122)
  - Trimester Plan, Heckinger Article (Box 135, Folder 1123)
  - Tuition, 1957-1965 (Box 136, Folder 1124-1125)
  - Tuition, Tuition Remission, June 1957 (Box 136, Folder 1126)
  - Tuition, Tuition Increase, June 1957 (Box 136, Folder 1127)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Reports and Schedule, 1964 (Box 136, Folder 1128)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Space Meeting, June 24 - 25, 1964 (Box 136, Folder 1129)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings,Campus Planning, Social Professions School, July 8-9, 1964 (Box 136, Folder 1130)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Campus Planning, Stadium, July 9-10, 1964 (Box 136, Folder 1131)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Campus Planning, Johnstown, July 13-14, 1964 (Box 136, Folder 1132)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Economic Growth, July 16-17 ,1964 (Box 136, Folder 1133)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Latin America Campus and Overseas Programs, July 20-22, 1964 (Box 136, Folder 1134)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Computer Science, July 27-28, 1964 (Box 136, Folder 1135)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Massive Endowment and Other Fund Raising, July 31-August 1, 1964 (Box 136, Folder 1136)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Knowledge Availability Systems, August 2-3, 1964 (Box 136, Folder 1137)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, CTC - The Education Continuum, August 4-5 (Canceled - Held September 11),1964 (Box 136, Folder 1138)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Reports and Schedule, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 1139)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Space Research Coordination Center, July 9, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 1140)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Region Campuses, July 11-12, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 1141)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Health Center, July 15, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 1142)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings,Biological Sciences, July 16 (Canceled) 1963 (Box 137, Folder 1143)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings,Knowledge Availability Systems, July 19-20, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 1144)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings,Year-Round Education, Chapters A - C, July 23-24, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 1145)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Year-Round Education, Chapters D - M, July 23-24, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 1146)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Latin America, July 30, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 1147)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Oakland Corporation, August 6, 1963 (Box 137, Folder 1148)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Reports and Schedule, 1962 (Box 137, Folder 1149)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Social Psychiatry, July 12, 1962 (Box 137, Folder 1150)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Information Retrieval, July 17, 1962 (Box 137, Folder 1151)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, July 12-14, 1961 (Box 137, Folder 1152)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, Industrial Civilization, July 17-19, 1961 (Box 138, Folder 1153)
  - Tumble Run Summer Meetings, 1960 (Box 138, Folder 1154)
  - Twenty-Year Club, 1941-1967 (Box 138, Folder 1155-1160)
  - T General
    - Tabor - Taylor, Harvey (Box 139, Folder 1161)
    - Taylor, John - Technoma (Box 139, Folder 1162)
    - Teckmeyer - Time (Box 139, Folder 1163)
    - Tuition Alliance (Box 139, Folder 1164)
    - Tuition Exchange - Tyler (Box 139, Folder 1165)
  - United Fund (Box 139, Folder 1166)
  - University Environmental Health and Safety, Committee on (Box 139, Folder 1167)
  - University Press, 1959 - 1965(1980) (Box 139, Folder 1168)
  - University Press, 1955 - 1958 (Box 139, Folder 1169)
  - Urban Regional Information Center (Box 140, Folder 1170)
  - U General
    - Un-American - United Nations (Box 140, Folder 1171)
    - United Negro - United States District (Box 140, Folder 1172)
    - United States Government - University Club (Box 140, Folder 1173)
    - University Directory - Urban (Box 140, Folder 1174)
  - Van de Graaff Accelerator (Box 140, Folder 1175)
  - Van de Graaff Accelerator, A Proposal for the Purchase and Installation of the Three Stage Van de Graaff Accelerator (Box 140, Folder 1176)
  - Van de Graaff Accelerator, Announcements and News Releases (Box 140, Folder 1177)
  - Van de Graaff Accelerator, Dedication Ceremonies (Box 140, Folder 1178)
  - Venezuelan Project (Box 141, Folder 1179)
  - V General
    - Valentine - Vaughn (Box 141, Folder 1180)
    - Venable - Vrona (Box 141, Folder 1181)
  - Warwick Terrace (Box 141, Folder 1182)
  - Water Pollution Laboratory (Box 141, Folder 1183)
  - West Virginia University (Box 141, Folder 1190)
  - Women's Education, Assistant to the Chancellor for (Box 142, Folder 1191)
  - WQED, 1956-1964 (Box 142, Folder 1.1921193E7)
  - Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic, 1956-1965 (Box 142, Folder 1184-1185)
  - Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic, Progress Report, 1951-1955 (Box 142, Folder 1186)
  - Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic, Chancellor's Council for WPIC (Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic) (Box 142, Folder 1187)
  - Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic, Pittsburgh Psychoanalytic Institute (Box 142, Folder 1188)
  - Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic, Social Psychiatry (Box 142, Folder 1189)
  - W General
    - Wachman - Washburn (Box 142, Folder 1194)
    - Washington - Wesley (Box 142, Folder 1195)
    - West - Westmoreland (Box 142, Folder 1196)
    - Whaley - William (Box 142, Folder 1197)
    - Williams - Williamsburg (Box 143, Folder 1198)
    - Willis - Wolfe (Box 143, Folder 1199)
    - Women's World (Box 143, Folder 1200)
    - WPGH - Wright (Box 143, Folder 1201)
    - Wriston - Wyoming (Box 143, Folder 1202)
  - X, Y, Z General
    - X and Y General (Box 143, Folder 1203)
    - Z General (Box 143, Folder 1204)
  - Convocation
    - Honors Convocation, 1958 (Box 144, Folder 1205)
      Honorary Degrees: Robert Frost Soloman, Bennett Freehof
    - Fall Convocation, Academic Disciplines Convocation and Honors Convocation, 1958-1959 (Box 144, Folder 1206)
      Archibald Mac Leish
    - Convocations and Honorary Degrees, 1959-1960 (Box 144, Folder 1207)
      Fall convocation, 1959; Honors Convocation 1960 (Pearl S. Buck); Fall Convocation 1960
    - Fall Convocation and Honors Convocations, 1961-1962 (Box 144, Folder 1208)
      Honorary Degrees: Earl Warren, Gene Kelly, Gladys Schmitt, William Steele, Edward Rynearson. Barbara Ward
    - Fall Convocation, Honors Convocation, Alumni Convocation, 1962-1963 (Box 144, Folder 1209)
      Honorary Degrees: Edward Teller and Homer Sylvester Brown, George B. Burkley, Frederick Franck.
    - Convocation, Honors, 1964 (Box 144, Folder 1210)
      Honorary Degree: Sir Charles Snow
    - Fall Convocation with Honorary Degrees, 1964 (Box 144, Folder 1211)
      Honorary Degrees: Sister M. Thomas Aquinas, Robert Brainard Corey, Solis Horwitz, Diosdalo Macapagal (speaker)
    - Honors Convocation, 1965 (Box 144, Folder 1212)
      Honorary Degrees: Lorin Maazel, Peter H. Odegard.
    - Fall Convocation, 1965 (Box 145, Folder 1213)
      Honorary Degrees: Leonard H. Marks, Harold Howland and Henry Steele Commager; Transcript of Commager's speech.
    - Commencement, February 1965 (Box 145, Folder 1214)
    - Commencement, June 1956 (Box 145, Folder 1215)
      Honorary Degrees: Judson A. Crane, Holgar J. Johnson, James G. Houston, Vernon F. Gallagher, and Irving W. Wilson.
    - Commencement - Correspondence, June 1956 (Box 145, Folder 1216)
    - Commencement, August 1956 (Box 145, Folder 1217)
    - Commencement, February 1957 (Box 145, Folder 1218)
      Honorary Degrees: Ralph Johnson Bunche, Gaylord p. Harnwell and Charles Bernard Nutting.
    - Commencement - Correspondence, February 1957 (Box 145, Folder 1219)
    - Commencement, June 1957 (Box 145, Folder 1220)
      Honorary Degrees: Roger Miles Blough, Harold Willis Dodds, Mervin J. Kelly, Robert Daniel Murphy and Arthur Boswick VanBuskirk
    - Commencement -Correspondence, June 1957 (Box 145, Folder 1221)
    - Commencement, June 1958 (Box 146, Folder 1222)
      Honorary Degrees: Frank Richard Denton, Robert DeBlois Calkins, Arthur Hays Sulzberger and Wernher VonBraun.
    - Commencement - Correspondence, June 1958 (Box 146, Folder 1223)
    - Commencement - Files on Honorary Degree Recipients and Speaker, June 1958 (Box 146, Folder 1224)
    - Commencement - Luncheon, June 1958 (Box 146, Folder 1225)
    - Commencement, June 1959 (Box 146, Folder 1226)
      Honorary Degrees: Park Hussey Martin, Jose Antonio Mora, Alfred Pritchard Sloan and Edward Augustus Weeks.
    - Commencement, June 1960 (Box 146, Folder 1227)
      Honorary Degrees: Henry John Heinz II, Courtney Craig Smith, Robert Douglas Stuart and Christian Archibald Herter.
    - Commencement - Correspondence, June 1960 (Box 146, Folder 1228)
    - Commencement, June 1961 (Box 147, Folder 1229)
      Honorary Degrees: Max Abramovitz, Eugene Carson Blake, David Dodds Henry, Thomas Parran and Elvis Jacob Stahr, Jr.
    - Commencement, June 1962 (Box 147, Folder 1230)
      Honorary Degrees: Katharine Elizabeth McBride, Wendell Meredith Stanley, Maxwell Davenport Taylor and John Joseph Wright.
    - Commencement, June 1963 (Box 147, Folder 1231)
      Honorary Degrees: William Oliver Baker, Carlyle Smith Beals, Alan Tower Waterman, James Edwin Webb and Harold Clayton Urey.
    - Commencement -Correspondence, June 1963 (Box 147, Folder 1232)
    - Commencement, June 1964 (Box 147, Folder 1233)
      Honorary Degrees: Shiyali Ramamrita Ranganathan, Claude Elwood Shannon, Warren Weaver and Lawrence Quincy Mumford.
- General Office Files, 1955-1965; II.
  - University Study Committee Reports for each Area, August 1965 (Box 148, Folder 1234)
  - Time Sheet for Chauffeur, 1960-1963 (Box 148, Folder 1235)
  - Plane Schedules, 1961-1963 (Box 148, Folder 1236)
  - Oct. 22, 1959 issue of This Week, October 22, 1959 (Box 148, Folder 1237)
    Appointment of Walter T. Stace as Third Visiting Andrew Mellon Professor and Clay and Denton to Board of Trustees
  - Resolution adopted by Senate of Pennsylvania on, commending University of Pittsburgh, along with two other institutions on twelve-month program, July 14, 1959 (Box 148, Folder 1238)
  - Proposed University By-Laws Revisions: Designations of graduate degrees for Graduate School of Public and International Affairs and School of Nursing and Adjustment of University fees, June 10, 1959 (Box 148, Folder 1239)
  - Joint Convocation for the Pittsburgh Bicentennial, May 12, 1959 (Box 148, Folder 1240)
  - Consideration of the use of Pitt Stadium as a Municipal Stadium and Graduate Degrees in Engineering, April 2, 1959 (Box 148, Folder 1241)
  - Announcements of the Gift from the A. W. Mellon Educational and Charitable Trusts for Endowed Professorships, Predoctoral, and Postdoctoral Fellowships (Box 148, Folder 1241)
  - Resolution by Board of Trustees approving articles on agreement on Health Center Hospitals campaign, dated, February 1959 (Box 148, Folder 1241)
  - Joint Committee on Faculty Participation in Policy- Making and Trimester Plan (Box 148, Folder 1242)
  - Archives of the Litchfield Administration (S.C. Crawford) (Box 148, Folder 1243)
  - Excerpt from Minutes of Executive Committee re: Authority to Negotiate for Forbes Field Purchase - Dedication of the Babcock Memorial Room, November 13, 1958, November 24, 1958 (Box 148, Folder 1244)
  - Organization Chart plus Board resolutions on appointments, Schenley and Ruskin properties, Forbes Field and Babcock Room, October 1958 (Box 149, Folder 1245)
  - Organization Chart and Job Descriptions, 1958 (Box 149, Folder 1246)
  - Faculty Manual, Relationship between the College of the Academic Disciplines and the School of Liberal Arts, Planning and Development, Educational Objectives, Trimester Planning, September 1958 (Box 149, Folder 1247)
  - Board of Trustees resolution on New Tenure Plan, first issue of The Pennsylvania Way, tuition Exchange with Carnegie Tech, Faculty Housing, and updated By-Laws for the University, June 1958 (Box 149, Folder 1248)
  - Resolutions changing the College to the School of Liberal Arts and Emeritus Status, Newsletter to Faculty, April 1958 (Box 149, Folder 1249)
  - Retirement from Administrative Assignments, Johnstown Center to Johnstown College, Establishment of General Studies, Trustees Emeritus, Stadium Lease, March 1958 (Box 149, Folder 1250)
  - Executive Committee Authorizing negotiations to purchase Ruskin Apartments and Tentative Terms for Ruskin Apartments Bonds, Buidling F of Schenley Park Apartments, February 1958 (Box 149, Folder 1251)
  - Tuition Remission Schedule, College Teaching Seminar, Criteria for Faculty, Land for Langley Hall, Purchase of Municipal Hospital, July 1957-December 1957 (Box 149, Folder 1252)
  - Establishment of Tuition and General University Fee, Letter to Students, QPA for Graduate Study, Change of name for School of Retailing, Approval of Sale of Student Union Bonds, June 1957 (Box 149, Folder 1253)
  - Board of College Advisors, Business Affairs, Tuition and Fee Structure, Part Time Insturctors, Authorization for Major Medical Expense Insurance, Area 8, May 1957 (Box 149, Folder 1254)
  - Summary Analysis of Gifts, Closing of Darragh St. (Area 8), 1946-1956 (Box 149, Folder 1255)
  - Change in Name of School of Social Work, March 1957 (Box 149, Folder 1256)
  - Winter 1956 - 1957 copy of Pitt: New Counseling Center and Computation and Data Processing Center and Polio Report: Mass Polio Shots Program, January 1957-February 1957 (Box 149, Folder 1257)
  - Authorization to establish Graduate School of Public Affairs, Tuition Increase, Creations of Boards of Visitors, Insurance and Retirement Programs, December 11, 1956 (Box 149, Folder 1258)
  - Graduate School of Public Affairs, Organization of Graduate Study, November 1956 (Box 149, Folder 1259)
  - Sabbatical Leave Policy, Sale of Properties: School of Pharmacy and 651 Morewood Avenue, Graduate School of Public Affairs, October 1956 (Box 149, Folder 1260)